Finding Aid for the Yvar Mikhashoff Trust for New Music Records, 1996-2011
State University of New York at Buffalo, Music Library
- 2009, XIII.; Item 2009-001-2009-120
  - Scores, 2009, D.; Item 2009-094-2009-120
    - Power, Karen Old Fashioned Chocolate Fondue Fountain, 2005-2006, 1 score (15 p.); 22 x 30 cm. (Box 83, Item 2009-110)
      For violin (using natural and artificial harmonics only) and piano (using inside the piano only).
    - Rusconi, Roberto, 1972- Isole nella Corrente, undated, 11 p. of music; 30 cm. (Box 83, Item 2009-111)
    - Russell, Jonathan, 1979- Metamorphosis #1, 2007, 16 p. of music; 28 cm. (Box 83, Item 2009-112)
    - Stout, Alastair Cave Paintings, 2005, 1 score (47 p.); 22 x 28 cm. (Box 83, Item 2009-113)
    - Tzortzis, Nicolas Desaxe (pour dix musiciens), 2007, 1 score (42 p.); 30 x 43 cm. (Box 83, Item 2009-114)
      For clarinet, bassoon, horn, trumpet in C, trombone (tenor/bass), percussion, violin, viola, cello, double bass.
    - Tzortzis, Nicolas Accordage du menteur, 2005-2007, 17 p. of music; 30 x 43 cm. (Box 83, Item 2009-115)
    - Tzortzis, Nicolas Mnesique (pour cinq musiciens), 2008, 1 score (40 p.); 30 x 43 cm. (Box 83, Item 2009-116)
      For flute, clarinet, violin, cello, and piano.
    - VanHassel, Dan Explosive Spontaneous, undated, 4 p. of music; 28 cm. (Box 83, Item 2009-117)
    - Watkins, Zachary (206)culture, 2004, 1 score (iii, 9 p.); 22 x 28 cm. (Box 83, Item 2009-118)
      For clarinet/bass clarinet and piano.
    - Du, Yun, 1977- Vicissitudes No. 1, undated, 1 score (46 p.); 22 x 37 cm. (Box 83, Item 2009-119)
      For clarinet, violoncello, contrabass, percussion, piano, and guitar.
    - Du, Yun, 1977- Vicissitudes No. 3, 2003, 1 score (55 p.); 31 cm. (Box 83, Item 2009-120)
      For chamber orchestra and narrator.
- 2010, XIV.; Item 2010-001-2010-237
  - Award recipients, 2010, A.; Item 2010-001-2010-002
    - Walentynowicz, Malgorzata, Bertelsmeier, Birke J., 1981- (Box 74, Item 2010-001)
    - Broome, David, Wollschleger, Scott (Box 74, Item 2010-002)
  - Applicants (Pianist and Composer), 2010, B.; Item 2010-003-2010-046
    - Antoniadis, Pavlos, Tzortzis, Nicolas (Box 74, Item 2010-003)
    - Antonov, Avguste, Sideris, Nikolas (Box 74, Item 2010-004)
    - Barelos, Stacey, Maloy, Kristopher (Box 74, Item 2010-005)
    - Barger, Laura, Podgursky, Jeremy (Box 74, Item 2010-006)
    - Beck, Steven, 1978-, Iglesia, Daniel (Box 74, Item 2010-007)
    - Camacho, Dionisio, Gil, José A. (Box 74, Item 2010-008)
    - Chai, Jenny Q., Seidl, Hannes, 1977- (Box 74, Item 2010-009)
    - Chen, Phyllis, Du, Yun, 1977- (Box 74, Item 2010-010)
    - Chien, Gloria, Castillo, Patrick, 1979- (Box 74, Item 2010-011)
    - Choi, Rosabel, Hron, Teresa (Box 74, Item 2010-012)
    - Choi, Seeun, Michaels, Joseph, 1977- (Box 74, Item 2010-013)
    - Chow, Vicky, Thomson, Ken, 1976- (Box 74, Item 2010-014)
    - Ding, Shiau-uen, Xie, Wenhui (Box 74, Item 2010-015)
    - Espigolé, Lluïsa, Faegri, Vegard (Box 74, Item 2010-016)
    - Françoise, Antoine, Peterson, Tom, 1985- (Box 74, Item 2010-017)
    - Fried, William, Ruviaro, Bruno (Box 74, Item 2010-018)
    - Gagnon, Benoît, Holbrook, Geof (Box 74, Item 2010-019)
    - Gu, Sandra, Epstein, Nomi (Box 74, Item 2010-020)
    - Kirkendoll, Michael, Van Brink, Matthew, 1978- (Box 74, Item 2010-021)
    - Ledger, Kate, Herbert, Johnny (Box 74, Item 2010-022)
    - Liatsou, Lenio, Maronidis, Dimitrios (Box 74, Item 2010-023)
    - Manzo, Emily, Welch, Matthew, 1976- (Box 74, Item 2010-024)
    - Mantzouratou, Dimitra, Dousis, George (Box 74, Item 2010-025)
    - Marks, Adam, Dietz, Christopher, 1977- (Box 74, Item 2010-026)
    - Mawhinney, Simon, 1976-, Molloy, Ryan (Box 74, Item 2010-027)
    - McGarry, Maria, Holstead, Rachel, 1978- (Box 74, Item 2010-028)
    - Meek, Scott, Baldwin, Daniel, 1978- (Box 74, Item 2010-029)
    - Mitchell, Bobby, 1985-, Sekhon, Baljinder Singh, II (Box 74, Item 2010-030)
    - Mizrahi, Michael, Dancigers, Mark (Box 75, Item 2010-031)
    - Morgulis, Tali, Maroney, Marcus (Box 75, Item 2010-032)
    - Nagai, Erico, Mehinovic, Vedran (Box 75, Item 2010-033)
    - Pestova, Xenia, Kojs, Juraj (Box 75, Item 2010-034)
    - Pfeffer, Nimrod David, Gilutz, Amit (Box 75, Item 2010-035)
    - Rabinovich, Roman, Porat, Matan (Box 75, Item 2010-036)
    - Rhodebeck, Jacob, Bithell, David, 1976- (Box 75, Item 2010-037)
    - Rosenkranz, Thomas, 1977-, Swendsen, Peter V. (Box 75, Item 2010-038)
    - Schaffer, Regina, Stiles, Sarah (Box 75, Item 2010-039)
    - Schlime´, Francesco Tristano, 1981-, Messina, Justin, 1980- (Box 75, Item 2010-040)
    - Schneider, Michael, Joyce, Molly, 1993- (Box 75, Item 2010-041)
    - Senekeremian, Harout, Gianopoulos, George N. (Box 75, Item 2010-042)
    - Venturini, Franco, Cacciatore, Maurilio (Box 75, Item 2010-043)
    - Walcerz, Filip, Blecharz, Wojciech, 1981- (Box 75, Item 2010-044)
    - Yeh, I-Chen, Carrizo, Andres (Box 75, Item 2010-045)
    - Yu, Ning, Akiho, Andy (Box 75, Item 2010-046)
  - Audio and video recordings, 2010, C.; Item 2010-047-2010-182
    Arranged in two alphabetical sequences: pianists then composers. Some headings have multiple entries.
    - Antoniadis, Pavlos (Box 76, Item 2010-047)
    - Antonov, Avguste (Box 76, Item 2010-048)
    - Antonov, Avguste (Box 76, Item 2010-049)
    - Barelos, Stacey (Box 76, Item 2010-050)
    - Barelos, Stacey (Box 76, Item 2010-051)
    - Barger, Laura (Box 76, Item 2010-052)
    - Barger, Laura (Box 76, Item 2010-053)
    - Beck, Steve (Box 76, Item 2010-054)
    - Beck, Steve (Box 76, Item 2010-055)
    - Broome, David (Box 76, Item 2010-056)
    - Broome, David (Box 76, Item 2010-057)
    - Camacho, Dionisio (Box 76, Item 2010-058)
    - Camacho, Dionisio (Box 76, Item 2010-059)
    - Chai, Jenny Q. (Box 76, Item 2010-060)
    - Chai, Jenny Q. (Box 76, Item 2010-061)
    - Chen, Phyllis (Box 76, Item 2010-062)
    - Chien, Gloria (Box 76, Item 2010-063)
    - Chien, Gloria (Box 76, Item 2010-064)
    - Chien, Gloria (Box 76, Item 2010-065)
    - Choi, Rosabel (Box 76, Item 2010-066)
    - Choi, Rosabel (Box 76, Item 2010-067)
    - Choi, Seeun (Box 76, Item 2010-068)
    - Chow, Vicky (Box 76, Item 2010-069)
    - Chow, Vicky (Box 76, Item 2010-070)
    - Ding, Shiau-uen (Box 76, Item 2010-071)
    - Ding, Shiau-uen (Box 76, Item 2010-072)
    - Espigolé, Lluïsa (Box 76, Item 2010-073)
    - Espigolé, Lluïsa (Box 76, Item 2010-074)
    - Françoise, Antoine (Box 76, Item 2010-075)
    - Françoise, Antoine (Box 76, Item 2010-076)
    - Françoise, Antoine (Box 76, Item 2010-077)
    - Fried, William (Box 76, Item 2010-078)
    - Fried, William (Box 76, Item 2010-079)
    - Fried, William (Box 76, Item 2010-080)
    - Gagnon, Benoît (Box 76, Item 2010-081)
    - Gagnon, Benoît (Box 76, Item 2010-082)
    - Gu, Sandra (Box 76, Item 2010-083)
    - Gu, Sandra (Box 76, Item 2010-084)
    - Holbrook, Geof (Box 76, Item 2010-085)
    - Kirkendoll, Michael (Box 76, Item 2010-086)
    - Kirkendoll, Michael (Box 76, Item 2010-087)
    - Ledger, Kate (Box 76, Item 2010-088)
    - Ledger, Kate (Box 76, Item 2010-089)
    - Liatsou, Lenio (Box 76, Item 2010-090)
    - Manzo, Emily (Box 76, Item 2010-091)
    - Manzo, Emily (Box 76, Item 2010-092)
    - Manzo, Emily (Box 76, Item 2010-093)
    - Mantzouratou, Dimitra (Box 77, Item 2010-094)
    - Mantzouratou, Dimitra (Box 77, Item 2010-095)
    - Marks, Adam (Box 77, Item 2010-096)
    - Marks, Adam (Box 77, Item 2010-097)
    - Mawhinney, Simon, 1976- (Box 77, Item 2010-098)
    - Mawhinney, Simon, 1976- (Box 77, Item 2010-099)
    - McGarry, Maria (Box 77, Item 2010-100)
    - McGarry, Maria (Box 77, Item 2010-101)
    - McGarry, Maria (Box 77, Item 2010-102)
    - Meek, Scott (Box 77, Item 2010-103)
    - Meek, Scott (Box 77, Item 2010-104)
    - Mitchell, Bobby, 1985- (Box 77, Item 2010-105)
    - Mitchell, Bobby, 1985- (Box 77, Item 2010-106)
    - Mizrahi, Michael (Box 77, Item 2010-107)
    - Mizrahi, Michael (Box 77, Item 2010-108)
    - Morgulis, Tali (Box 77, Item 2010-109)
    - Morgulis, Tali (Box 77, Item 2010-110)
    - Nagai, Erico (Box 77, Item 2010-111)
    - Nagai, Erico (Box 77, Item 2010-112)
    - Pestova, Xenia (Box 77, Item 2010-113)
    - Pestova, Xenia (Box 77, Item 2010-114)
    - Pfeffer, Nimrod David (Box 77, Item 2010-115)
    - Pfeffer, Nimrod David (Box 77, Item 2010-116)
    - Porat, Matan (Box 77, Item 2010-117)
    - Rabinovich, Roman (Box 77, Item 2010-118)
    - Rabinovich, Roman (Box 77, Item 2010-119)
    - Rhodebeck, Jacob (Box 77, Item 2010-120)
    - Rosenkranz, Thomas, 1977- (Box 77, Item 2010-121)
    - Rosenkranz, Thomas, 1977- (Box 77, Item 2010-122)
    - Schaffer, Regina (Box 77, Item 2010-123)
    - Schaffer, Regina (Box 77, Item 2010-124)
    - Schlime´, Francesco Tristano, 1981- (Box 77, Item 2010-125)
    - Schlime´, Francesco Tristano, 1981- (Box 77, Item 2010-126)
    - Schneider, Michael (Box 77, Item 2010-127)
    - Schneider, Michael (Box 77, Item 2010-128)
    - Senekeremian, Harout (Box 77, Item 2010-129)
    - Venturini, Franco (Box 77, Item 2010-130)
    - Venturini, Franco (Box 78, Item 2010-131)
    - Venturini, Franco (Box 78, Item 2010-132)
    - Walcerz, Filip (Box 78, Item 2010-133)
    - Walcerz, Filip (Box 78, Item 2010-134)
    - Walcerz, Filip (Box 78, Item 2010-135)
    - Walentynowicz, Malgorzata (Box 78, Item 2010-136)
    - Walentynowicz, Malgorzata (Box 78, Item 2010-137)
    - Xie, Wenhui (Box 78, Item 2010-138)
    - Yeh, I-Chen (Box 78, Item 2010-139)
    - Yeh, I-Chen (Box 78, Item 2010-140)
    - Yu, Ning (Box 78, Item 2010-141)
    - Yu, Ning (Box 78, Item 2010-142)
    - Akiho, Andy (Box 78, Item 2010-143)
    - Baldwin, Daniel, 1978- (Box 78, Item 2010-144)
    - Bertelsmeier, Birke J., 1981- (Box 78, Item 2010-145)
    - Bithell, David, 1976- (Box 78, Item 2010-146)
    - Blecharz, Wojciech, 1981- (Box 78, Item 2010-147)
    - Cacciatore, Mauricio (Box 78, Item 2010-148)
    - Carrizo, Andres (Box 78, Item 2010-149)
    - Dancigers, Mark (Box 78, Item 2010-150)
    - Dietz, Christopher, 1977- (Box 78, Item 2010-151)
    - Dousis, George (Box 78, Item 2010-152)
    - Epstein, Nomi (Box 78, Item 2010-153)
    - Faegri, Vegard (Box 78, Item 2010-154)
    - Gianopoulos, George N. (Box 78, Item 2010-155)
    - Gil, José A. (Box 78, Item 2010-156)
    - Gilutz, Amit (Box 78, Item 2010-157)
    - Herbert, Johnny (Box 78, Item 2010-158)
    - Holstead, Rachel, 1978- (Box 78, Item 2010-159)
    - Hron, Teresa (Box 78, Item 2010-160)
    - Iglesia, Daniel (Box 78, Item 2010-161)
    - Joyce, Molly, 1993- (Box 78, Item 2010-162)
    - Kojs, Juraj (Box 78, Item 2010-163)
    - Maloy, Kristopher (Box 78, Item 2010-164)
    - Maroney, Marcus (Box 78, Item 2010-165)
    - Maronidis, Dimitris (Box 78, Item 2010-166)
    - Mehinovic, Vedran (Box 78, Item 2010-167)
    - Messina, Justin, 1980- (Box 79, Item 2010-168)
    - Michaels, Joseph, 1977- (Box 79, Item 2010-169)
    - Peterson, Tom, 1985- (Box 79, Item 2010-170)
    - Podgursky, Jeremy (Box 79, Item 2010-171)
    - Ruviaro, Bruno (Box 79, Item 2010-172)
    - Sekhon, Baljinder Singh, II (Box 79, Item 2010-173)
    - Sideris, Nikolas (Box 79, Item 2010-174)
    - Stiles, Sarah (Box 79, Item 2010-175)
    - Swendsen, Peter V. (Box 79, Item 2010-176)
    - Thomson, Ken, 1976- (Box 79, Item 2010-177)
    - Tzortzis, Nicolas (Box 79, Item 2010-178)
    - Van Brink, Matthew, 1978- (Box 79, Item 2010-179)
    - Welch, Matthew, 1976- (Box 79, Item 2010-180)
    - Wollschleger, Scott (Box 79, Item 2010-181)
    - Du, Yun, 1977- (Box 79, Item 2010-182)
  - Scores, 2010, D.; Item 2010-183-2010-237
    - Akiho, Andy Vick(y/i), 2008, 10 p. of music; 28 x 44 cm. (Box 83, Item 2010-183)
      For solo prepared piano.
    - Baldwin, Daniel, 1978- Sonata for oboe and piano, undated, 1 score (23 p.); 28 cm. (Box 83, Item 2010-184)
      For oboe and piano.
    - Bertelsmeier, Birke J., 1981- Kurz vor'm, undated, 1 score (85 p.); 30 cm. (Box 84, Item 2010-185)
    - Bertelsmeier, Birke J., 1981- Spiele, undated, 1 score (16 p.); 21 x 30 cm. (Box 84, Item 2010-186)
    - Bithell, David, 1976- Temporary Structures, 2009, 1 score (29 p.); 22 x 28 cm. (Box 84, Item 2010-187)
      For oboe, clarinet, alto saxophone, viola, cello, and piano.
    - Blecharz, Wojtek xyz, 2007-2008, 1 score (21 p.); 22 x 28 cm. (Box 84, Item 2010-188)
    - Cacciatore, Maurilio Nelsalen, 2007, 1 score (unpaged); 21 x 30 cm. (Box 84, Item 2010-189)
      For flute, bass clarinet, violin, piano, and percussions.
    - Carrizo, Andres Encuentros, 2008-2009, 1 score (12 p.); 28 x 44 cm. (Box 84, Item 2010-190)
      For saxophone (tenor and alto), piano, and percussion.
    - Castillo, Patrick, 1979- Lola, 2004, 1 score (25 p.); 28 cm. (Box 84, Item 2010-191)
    - Dancigers, Mark Bright Motion, 2007, 12 p. of music; 28 cm. (Box 84, Item 2010-192)
    - Dietz, Christopher, 1977- Five Reflections on the Rubaiyat of Omar Khayyam, 2009, 30 p. of music; 31 cm. (Box 84, Item 2010-193)
    - Dousis, George Five Moments, 2008, 2, 5, 2, 5, 4 p. of music; 30 cm. (Box 84, Item 2010-194)
    - Epstein, Nomi Till, 2003, 5 p. of music; 22 x 28 cm. (Box 84, Item 2010-195)
    - Fagri, Vegard Somsol, undated, 52 p. of music; 30 cm. (Box 84, Item 2010-196)
    - Gilutz, Amit Autumn Days..., undated, [11] p. of music; 28 cm. (Box 84, Item 2010-197)
    - Gilutz, Amit 12 pieces from The Cat Saved My Life: a musical reading in Dalia Ravikovich's poetry, 2009, 1 score (53 p.); 22 x 28 cm. (Box 84, Item 2010-198)
      For flute, clarinet, bassoon, piano, mezzo-soprano, violin, and cello.
    - Gianopoulos, George N. Five Pieces for solo piano, op. 15, 2009, [39] p. of music; 28 cm. (Box 84, Item 2010-199)
    - Gianopoulos, George N. Two Fantasies for solo piano, op. 5, 2006-2008, [30] p. of music; 28 cm. (Box 84, Item 2010-200)
    - Gil, J. Antonio Wormhole por la Numero Dos, 2008, 18 p. of music; 28 cm. (Box 84, Item 2010-201)
    - Herbert, Johnny Re(-)presenT, 2007-2008, 17 p. of music; 30 cm. (Box 84, Item 2010-202)
    - Holbrook, Geof Trans/Fusion, 2005, 1 score (20 p.); 21 x 30 cm. (Box 85, Item 2010-203)
      For piano and percussion.
    - Holstead, Rachel, 1978- If I Could Rule the World, 2005, 1 score (39 p.); 30 cm. (Box 85, Item 2010-204)
      For piano, violin, girls' choir, and orchestra.
    - Hron, Terri Pallavi Masala, 2004, 1 score (8 p.); 22 x 28 cm. (Box 85, Item 2010-205)
      For prepared piano and percussion.
    - Iglesia, Daniel Advanced Reservations, 2005, 1 score (18 p.); 28 cm. (Box 85, Item 2010-206)
      For piano and computer.
    - Joyce, Molly, 1993- Finger Painting, 2009, 1 score (12 p.); 28 cm. (Box 85, Item 2010-207)
    - Joyce, Molly, 1993- Funeral in my Brain, 2009, 1 score (8 p.); 28 cm. (Box 85, Item 2010-208)
      For tenor solo and piano.
    - Kojs, Juraj Three Movements, 2004, 1 score (18 p.); 22 x 29 cm. (Box 85, Item 2010-209)
      For unprepared piano and electronics.
    - Maloy, Kristopher Uwohali, 2009, 9 p. of music; 28 cm. (Box 85, Item 2010-210)
    - Maroney, Marcus Karl Cinque Ricordi, 1999, 22 p. of music; 28 cm. (Box 85, Item 2010-211)
    - Maronidis, Dimitris Idiomorphia, 2007, 17 p. of music; 30 cm. (Box 85, Item 2010-212)
      For prepared piano.
    - Mehinovic, Vedran Parhelia, 2006, 1 score (11 p.); 28 cm. (Box 85, Item 2010-213)
    - Messina, Justin, 1980- NYTectonics: 4 City Bridges, 2006, [8] p. of music; 28 cm. (Box 85, Item 2010-214)
    - Michaels, Joseph, 1977- Improvisation Games, 2009, 1 score ([15] p.); 30 cm. (Box 85, Item 2010-215)
      For variable instrumentation.
    - Michaels, Joseph, 1977- Newport Beach in the '70s, 2009, 1 score (16 p.); 21 x 30 cm. (Box 85, Item 2010-216)
      For 2 violins, cello, and harpsichord.
    - Michaels, Joseph, 1977- Schtick, 2009, 1 score (59 p.); 21 x 30 cm. (Box 85, Item 2010-217)
      For piano 4-hands and playback.
    - Molloy, Ryan Carthage Harbour, 2009, 1 score (ii, 13 p.); 30 x 42 cm. (Box 85, Item 2010-218)
    - Peterson, Tom, 1985- Sonatina for piano, undated, 9 p. of music; 28 cm. (Box 85, Item 2010-219)
    - Podgursky, Jeremy Nonsense or Sorcery?#%*!, 2006, 1 score (38 p.); 22 x 28 cm. (Box 85, Item 2010-220)
      For violin, cello, and piano.
    - Porat, Matan Daniel ...for piano, 2006, 17 p. of music; 30 cm. (Box 85, Item 2010-221)
    - Ruviaro, Bruno Sete Vazios, 2006, 14 p. of music; 28 cm. (Box 86, Item 2010-222)
    - Seidl, Hannes, 1977- Die Anderen - Jetzt Neu!, 2009, 1 score (10 p.); 30 cm. + 1 sound disc (4 3/4 in.) (Box 86, Item 2010-223)
      For piano and CD.
    - Sekhon, Baljinder Gradient, 2008, 1 score (13 p.); 36 cm. (Box 86, Item 2010-224)
      For saxophone and piano.
    - Sideris, Nikolas The City Under Different Eyes, 2008, 15 p. of music; 30 cm. (Box 86, Item 2010-225)
      For sampled piano.
    - Stiles, Sarah, composer #1, undated, 12 p. of music; 28 cm. (Box 86, Item 2010-226)
    - Swendsen, Peter V. Preparations No. 3, 2003, 1 score ([8], 6 p.); 22 x 28 cm. (Box 86, Item 2010-227)
      For amplified prepared piano and stereophonic tape.
    - Thomson, Ken, 1976- seasonal.disorder, 2008, 1 score (29 p.); 22 x 28 cm. (Box 86, Item 2010-228)
      For bass clarinet, cello, electric guitar, piano, contrabass, 4-piece drumset, and keyboard.
    - Tzortzis, Nicolas L'accordage du menteur, 2005-2007, 17 p. of music; 30 x 42 cm. (Box 86, Item 2010-229)
    - Tzortzis, Nicolas Mnesique, 2008, 1 score (40 p.); 30 x 42 cm. (Box 86, Item 2010-230)
    - Van Brink, Matthew, 1978- Sparkle Epoxiplast 2000, 2006, 20 p. of music; 31 cm. (Box 86, Item 2010-231)
    - Welch, Matthew, 1976- Borges and The Other #1: a one-act chamber opera, 2007, 1 score (24, 38, 56, 19 p.); 22 x 28 cm. (Box 86, Item 2010-232)
      For soprano, flute, solo viola, electric guitar, piano, vibraphone, drum set, and bass guitar.
    - Wollschleger, Scott Secret Machines no. 5, 2009, 1 score ([15] p.); 28 cm. (Box 86, Item 2010-233)
      For various instrumentation.
    - Xie, Wenhui Piano Concerto I and II, 2004, 1 score (45 p.); 36 cm. (Box 86, Item 2010-234)
      For piano and orchestra.
    - Xie, Wenhui Sonetti a Orfeo I, No. IX, 2009, 1 score (26 p.); 36 cm. (Box 86, Item 2010-235)
      For soprano and instrumental ensemble.
    - Xie, Wenhui Space, 2006, 8 p. of music; 28 cm. (Box 86, Item 2010-236)
    - Du, Yun, 1977- Vicissitudes No. 1, undated, 1 score (46 p.); 22 x 36 cm. (Box 86, Item 2010-237)
- 2011, XV.; Item 2011-001-2011-195
  - Award recipients, 2011, A.; Item 2011-001-2011-003
    - Chai, Jenny Q., Wang, Ashley Fu-Tsun (Box 87, Item 2011-001)
    - Kirkendoll, Michael, Ivanova, Vera (Box 87, Item 2011-002)
    - Rozenkranz, Thomas, Dietz, Christopher, 1977- (Box 87, Item 2011-003)
  - Applicants (Pianist and Composer), 2011, B.; Item 2011-004-2010-038
    - Antoniadis, Pavlos, Tzortzis, Nicolas (Box 87, Item 2011-004)
    - Barelos, Stacey, Maloy, Kristopher (Box 87, Item 2011-005)
    - Beridze, Alexander, Oakley (Oaklei), George (Box 87, Item 2011-006)
    - Burger, Cole, Williams, Charlie (Box 87, Item 2011-007)
    - Chan, Claudia, Goddard, Christopher (Box 87, Item 2011-008)
    - Chow, Vicky, Akiho, Andy (Box 87, Item 2011-009)
    - Ciach, Brian, Williams, Natalie, 1977- (Box 87, Item 2011-010)
    - De Vleeschhouwer, Ward, Seo, Ju Ri (Box 87, Item 2011-011)
    - Friend, David, Wohl, David (Box 87, Item 2011-012)
    - Go, Aura, Neustadter, Garth (Box 87, Item 2011-013)
    - Hanick, Conor Llewellyn, Ciupinski, Jakub (Box 87, Item 2011-014)
    - Johnson, Kari, Blasco, Scott, 1978- (Box 87, Item 2011-015)
    - Kallay, Aron, Schankler, Isaac (Box 87, Item 2011-016)
    - Kanga, Zubin, Mark, Brian (Box 87, Item 2011-017)
    - Keller, Simone, Lee, Wendy Wan-Ki (Box 87, Item 2011-018)
    - Kim, Euntaek, Moya, Reinaldo (Box 87, Item 2011-019)
    - Kirchoff, Keith, VanHassel, Dan (Box 87, Item 2011-020)
    - Kwan, Mabel, Galindo, Gilbert (Box 87, Item 2011-021)
    - Ledger, Kate, Evanoff, Ray (Box 88, Item 2011-022)
    - Liviana, Angelica, Isaiah, Lee Chie Tsang (Box 88, Item 2011-023)
    - Maebayashi, Nao, Emfietzis, Gregory (Box 88, Item 2011-024)
    - McCright, Matthew, Cerrone, Christopher (Box 88, Item 2011-025)
    - Phillips, Nicholas Scott, 1978-, Broberg, Kirsten (Box 88, Item 2011-026)
    - Sandee, Laura, Iturralde, Carlos (Box 88, Item 2011-027)
    - Schaffer, Regina, Dicke, Ian, 1982- (Box 88, Item 2011-028)
    - Shevtsov, Yegor, Noble, Andrew R. (Box 88, Item 2011-029)
    - Shteinberg, Dmitri, Kolm, Jonathan (Box 88, Item 2011-030)
    - Smith, Simon, 1983-, Smith, Neil Thomas (Box 88, Item 2011-031)
    - Swayne, Adam, Holloway-Nahum, Aaron (Box 88, Item 2011-032)
    - Tedeschi, Simon, 1981-, Solitro, Tony (Box 88, Item 2011-033)
    - Theodorakis, Ermis, Seglias, Zesses (Box 88, Item 2011-034)
    - Torquati, Emanuele, 1978-, Carter, Ryan, 1980- (Box 88, Item 2011-035)
    - Venturini, Franco, Sarto, Andrea (Box 88, Item 2011-036)
    - Yang, Jing, Adams, Samuel (Box 88, Item 2011-037)
    - Yip, Michelle, Chen, Hsin-Lei (Box 88, Item 2011-038)
  - Audio and video recordings, 2011, C.; Item 2011-039-2011-153
    - Antoniadis, Pavlos (Box 89, Item 2011-039)
    - Barelos, Stacey (Box 89, Item 2011-040)
    - Barelos, Stacey (Box 89, Item 2011-041)
    - Beridze, Alexander (Box 89, Item 2011-042)
    - Beridze, Alexander (Box 89, Item 2011-043)
    - Burger, Cole (Box 89, Item 2011-044)
    - Burger, Cole (Box 89, Item 2011-045)
    - Chai, Jenny Q. (Box 89, Item 2011-046)
    - Chai, Jenny Q. (Box 89, Item 2011-047)
    - Chai, Jenny Q. (Box 89, Item 2011-048)
    - Chai, Jenny Q. (Box 89, Item 2011-049)
    - Chai, Jenny Q. (Box 89, Item 2011-050)
    - Chan, Claudia (Box 89, Item 2011-051)
    - Chan, Claudia (Box 89, Item 2011-052)
    - Chow, Vicky (Box 89, Item 2011-053)
    - Chow, Vicky (Box 89, Item 2011-054)
    - Ciach, Brian (Box 89, Item 2011-055)
    - Ciach, Brian (Box 89, Item 2011-056)
    - De Vleeschhouwer, Ward (Box 89, Item 2011-057)
    - Friend, David (Box 89, Item 2011-058)
    - Friend, David (Box 89, Item 2011-059)
    - Go, Aura (Box 89, Item 2011-060)
    - Go, Aura (Box 89, Item 2011-061)
    - Hanick, Conor L. (Box 89, Item 2011-062)
    - Hanick, Conor L. (Box 89, Item 2011-063)
    - Johnson, Kari (Box 89, Item 2011-064)
    - Johnson, Kari (Box 89, Item 2011-065)
    - Johnson, Kari (Box 89, Item 2011-066)
    - Kallay, Aron (Box 89, Item 2011-067)
    - Kallay, Aron (Box 89, Item 2011-068)
    - Kanga, Zubin (Box 89, Item 2011-069)
    - Kanga, Zubin (Box 89, Item 2011-070)
    - Kanga, Zubin (Box 89, Item 2011-071)
    - Keller, Simone (Box 89, Item 2011-072)
    - Keller, Simone (Box 89, Item 2011-073)
    - Kim, Euntaek (Box 89, Item 2011-074)
    - Kirchoff, Keith (Box 89, Item 2011-075)
    - Kirchoff, Keith (Box 89, Item 2011-076)
    - Kirkendoll, Michael (Box 89, Item 2011-077)
    - Kirkendoll, Michael (Box 89, Item 2011-078)
    - Kwan, Mabel (Box 89, Item 2011-079)
    - Kwan, Mabel (Box 89, Item 2011-080)
    - Ledger, Kate (Box 89, Item 2011-081)
    - Ledger, Kate (Box 89, Item 2011-082)
    - Liviana, Angelica (Box 89, Item 2011-083)
    - Maebayasho, Nao (Box 90, Item 2011-084)
    - Maebayasho, Nao (Box 90, Item 2011-085)
    - McCright, Matthew (Box 90, Item 2011-086)
    - McCright, Matthew (Box 90, Item 2011-087)
    - Phillips, Nicholas Scott, 1978- (Box 90, Item 2011-088)
    - Phillips, Nicholas Scott, 1978- (Box 90, Item 2011-089)
    - Rozenkranz, Thomas (Box 90, Item 2011-090)
    - Sandee, Laura (Box 90, Item 2011-091)
    - Sandee, Laura (Box 90, Item 2011-092)
    - Schaffer, Regina (Box 90, Item 2011-093)
    - Schaffer, Regina (Box 90, Item 2011-094)
    - Schaffer, Regina (Box 90, Item 2011-095)
    - Shevtsov, Yegor (Box 90, Item 2011-096)
    - Shevtsov, Yegor (Box 90, Item 2011-097)
    - Shteinberg, Dmitri (Box 90, Item 2011-098)